language:
  description: ":robot_face::exclamation: :arrow_right: :question:"
plugins:
  help:
    description: ":question: :robot_face::exclamation:"
    commands:
      help:
        command: ":question:"
        description: ":page_facing_up:"
        texts:
          response_text: >
            :eye: :page_facing_up:
            !:question: :arrow_right: :house_with_garden:
      intro:
        command: ":robot_face:"
        description: ":robot_face:"
        texts:
          response_text: ":robot_face::exclamation"
          attach_title: ":hand: :wrench:"
          attach_text: >
            /igor :question: :arrow_right: :page_facing_up:
      tellme:
        command: ":robot_face: :hammer_and_wrench:"
        description: ":robot_face: :hammer_and_wrench:"
        texts:
          response_text: ":robot_face: :hammer_and_wrench: :exclamation:"
          github_text: "https://github.com/ArjenSchwarz/igor :arrow_right: :hammer_and_wrench:"
          site_text: "https://ig.nore.me/projects/igor :arrow_right: :book:"
      whoami:
        command: ":neutral_face:"
        description: ":hammer_and_wrench: :neutral_face:"
        texts:
          response_text: ":stuck_out_tongue_winking:"
          attach_title: ":speaking_head_in_silhouette:"

  randomTumblr:
    description: ":robot_face: :arrow_right: :game_die: Tumblr :grey_question:"
    commands:
      tumblr:
        command: ":stuck_out_tongue:"
        description: ":game_die: Tumblr"
      specifictumblr:
        command: ":stuck_out_tongue: [replace]"
        description: ":game_die: [replace] tumblr"

  weather:
    description: ":robot_face: :arrow_right: :sunny::grey_question: Default: [replace]"
    commands:
      weather:
        command: ":sunny: [city]"
        description: ":sunny: :grey_question:"
        texts:
          response_text: ":sunny:"
          wind: ":wind_blowing_face:"
          temperature: ":thermometer:"
          humidity: ":droplet:"
      forecast:
        command: ":crystal_ball: [city]"
        description: "7 :calendar: :crystal_ball::grey_question:"
        texts:
          response_text: ":crystal_ball:"
          wind: ":wind_blowing_face:"
          min_temperature: ":arrow_down: :thermometer:"
          max_temperature: ":arrow_up: :thermometer:"
          humidity: ":droplet:"

  status:
    description: ":robot_face: :arrow_right: :thumbsup: :thumbsdown::grey_question:"
    commands:
      status:
        command: ":thumbsup::thumbsdown:"
        description: ":thumbsup: :thumbsdown: :grey_question:"
        texts:
          response_text: ":thumbsup: :thumbsdown: :grey_question:"
      status_aws:
        command: ":thumbsup::thumbsdown: aws"
        description: ":thumbsup: :thumbsdown: :page_facing_up: :grey_question: AWS"
        texts:
          response_text: ":thumbsup: :thumbsdown: :grey_question:"
          nr_issues: ":hash: :boom:"
          nr_resolved_issues: ":hash: :face_with_head_bandage:"
          ok: ":thumbsup:"
          more_details: "*:chart_with_upwards_trend: aws* :arrow_right: :page_facing_up:"
      status_url:
        command: ":thumbsup::thumbsdown: [url]"
        description: ":thumbsup: :thumbsdown: :grey_question:"
        texts:
          response_text: ":thumbsup: :thumbsdown::grey_question:"
          good: ":thumbsup:"
          bad: ":thumbsdown:"
      status_service:
        command: ":thumbsup::thumbsdown: [service]"
        description: ":thumbsup: :thumbsdown: :grey_question: [replace]"
        texts:
          response_text: ":thumbsup: :thumbsdown::grey_question:"

  xkcd:
    description: ":robot_face: :arrow_right: XKCD"
    commands:
      xkcd:
        command: ":pencil2:"
        description: ":pencil2: XKCD"
        texts:
          response_text: "XKCD :hash:"
      xkcd_random:
        command: ":pencil2: :game_die:"
        description: ":game_die: XKCD"
      xkcd_specific:
        command: ":pencil2: [nr]"
        description: "XKCD :hash:"

  remember:
    description: ":robot_face: :arrow_right: :frame_with_picture:"
    commands:
      remember:
        command: ":thinking_face: [name] [url]"
        description: ":thinking_face: :frame_with_picture: :grey_exclamation:"
        texts:
          response_text: "[replace] :arrow_right: :frame_with_picture:"
          forbidden: ":crossed_swords:"
      show:
        command: ":frame_with_picture: [name]"
        description: ":frame_with_picture:"
        texts:
          no_result: ¯\_(ツ)_/¯
      showall:
        command: ":frame_with_picture: :earth_africa"
        description: ":frame_with_picture: :frame_with_picture: :frame_with_picture:"
        texts:
          response_text: ":frame_with_picture:"
          no_result: ¯\_(ツ)_/¯
      forget:
        command: ":zipper_mouth_face: [name]"
        description: ":frame_with_picture: :arrow_right: :zipper_mouth_face:"
        texts:
          response_text: ":zipper_mouth_face:"
          forbidden: ":crossed_swords:"
